<resources>
    <string name="app_name">QuizApp</string>
    <string-array name="quiz_themes">
        <item>General Knowledge</item>
        <item>Science and Computers</item>
        <item>Animals</item>
        <item>Geography</item>
        <item>Art</item>
        <item>Mythology</item>
        <item>History</item>
        <item>Sports</item>
        <item>Film</item>
        <item>TV</item>
        <item>Politics</item>
        <item>Math</item>
        <item>Books</item>
        <item>Vehicle</item>
        <item>Music</item>
        <item>Video Games</item>
        <item>Nature</item>
        <item>Anime</item>
        <item>Board Games</item>
        <item>Cartoon</item>
        <item>Gadget</item>
        <item>Comic</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="quiz_difficulty">
        <item>easy</item>
        <item>medium</item>
        <item>hard</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="ToS">
        This terms of service is the binding agreement to using the services of this application. Please
        read the terms of service and the privacy policy before accepting. Using this application, no illegal
        or malicious activity is allowed. Additionally, this uses Open Trivia Database by PixelTail Games LLC
        who\'s terms of services also in effect. \n \n
        The copyright of the questions is by Open Trivia Database by PixelTail Games LLC. \n \n
        By using this product you agree to be communicating with us and PixelTail Games LLC. Anytime you
        send an email or any form of communication, you hereby consent to receive communication from us.
        Additionally, by accepting this agreement, you agree that the laws of your country will govern these
        terms and services or any dispute between us and you. \n \n
        You are granted access to a licence to use this application for personal use. \n \n
        You are solely responsible for your account and all activities on your account. \n \n
        For additional questions or comments, please contact us at rd167956@hotmail.com
    </string>
    <string name="PrivacyPolicy">
        For our commitment to protect your privacy, this is a statement to provide you with the information
        regarding what and how your data will be used. \n \n
        This application does not request any personal, finical or legal data. However, all data provide
        additionally in any text form will be saved. Additionally, any information gathered by your performance
        on the quizzes as well as your preferred themes and difficulties will be saved to provide you with
        the best experience specialized to you, the user. \n \n
        We also require access to the internet that could be logged and collected, including your protocol address,
        browser type, settings, services and cookie data. These logs are only used to increase your experience and
        will not be used by us for any reason. \n \n
        Other recipients of your data could include Open Trivia Database by PixelTail Games LLC when requesting
        data from their API \n \n
        For additional questions or comments, please contact us at rd167956@hotmail.com
    </string>
</resources>